

HORAKUNG THONG

Frontend Developer {}



About me

Hello, I'm a Frontend Developer and Software Engineer, passionate about programming and constantly learning new techniques. I have experience in developing websites and interactive technology programs for both on-ground and online events. My expertise extends to developing AR/VR filters and writing various web programs using available developer tools.



064-637-9555



pt_moss17782@hotmail.com



8/95 Pruksa Ville 85 Liap Khlong Thawi Road, Bang Khae Nuea ,Bang Khae Bangkok 10160

LANGUAGE

- Endlish
- Thai

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- HTML/CSS
- C#

HOBBY

- Guitar
- Reading book
- Play game/board game
- Exercise

EXPERIENCE

Frontend developer

MagicBox solution (February 2023 - July 2024)

• Developed and maintained both websites and mobile applications using front-end frameworks, ensuring smooth integration between back-end systems and front-end applications.

Web developer

VIZ Studio

(April 2020 - November 2023)

- Created websites with AR experiences and filter effects for sharing on social platforms.
- Developed game content using Game Engines.

Interactive media and Game developer

Anyi media

(August 2018- March 2020)

• Interactive 3D Developer with experience in crafting unique experiences that combine interactive elements with online events.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree Media digital technology (MDT)

king mongkut's university of technology thonburi 2014-2018

High School Certificate equivalent

assumption college thonburi 2002-2014

WEB FRAMEWORK

React 90%

70% Next.js

Vue.is 40%

70% React native